So friends, ICICI LBRD has disclosed its Quarter 3
numbers.  The data is given in lax.
I will convert it into crores and
tell you.  So see, the total income of the company in this
quarter has been Rs 6610 crore.
In the last quarter it was Rs 6582 crore and
last year the company had generated an income of Rs 5882 crore.
So our yearly quarterly income is
increasing quite well.  Let's talk about the
net premium of the company.  So the
company has earned a net premium of Rs 5685 crore in this quarter.
Whereas
in the last quarter,
net premium of Rs 5616 or Rs 5651 crore
was earned and last year the net premium of the company was
seen to be Rs 545 crore.  So
we are also seeing the net premium of the company increasing yearly and quarterly.  Let's talk about the
company's expenses.  So the company's
expenses for this quarter were Rs 639 crore.
In the previous quarter, it was ₹5830 crore and
last year the company had incurred expenses of ₹5197 crore.
So
we are also seeing the company's expenses increasing yearly and quarterly.
Talking about the net profit of the company, the
profit of the company this quarter has been Rs
658 crore.  In the last quarter it
was Rs 819 crore and last year the
company had generated a profit of Rs 724 crore.  So
we are seeing a decline in yearly quarterly profits.  The
reason behind this is that
we are seeing the company's provisions and company
expenses.  Talking about EPS, the
company's EPS for this quarter is
₹13.25.  Last quarter EPS was ₹16.49
49 and last year EPS of ₹14.63 was
generated by the company.  So
we are seeing a decline in the yearly quarterly EPS also.
So, if we talk about the overall numbers, the
company has shown a great performance on the top line
but
due to the provisions and expenses of the company, the
bottom line of the company is seen falling.
So you can say that we may see some negative
impact on the company's shares tomorrow.
So friends, these were the
numbers of ICICI LBT.  I hope
you liked the video.  If you liked it, please
like the video and
subscribe to our channel for more such updates.
See you in the next video, till then
thanks.